https://www.wagnermeters.com/privacy-policy/

My Account
0 items
800-634-9961
MenuRapid RH®To PurchaseShop NowFind a Rapid RH® DistributorAccessoriesApps for Mobile DevicesC555 Concrete Moisture MeterDataMaster™ L6 AppSmart Logger™Using the Rapid RH®Rapid RH® InstallationRapid RH® Manual (pdf)RH Testing TimeAdjusting for Service TempDangers of MVERWhy the Rapid RH®?Why RH Is THE AccurateSlab Moisture TestWhy You Should Use Relative Humidity (RH) TestingLearn MoreRapid RH L6 OverviewFree WebinarRH Testing Training VideosConcrete MoistureKnowledgeConcrete Flooring NewsletterBecome a Wagner Meters Authorized DistributorDownloads & SupportRapid RH® Test Results Form (pdf)ASTM F2170 Checklist (pdf)ASTM F2170 Checklist – Español (pdf)Rapid RH® Spec (pdf)Concrete Flooring FAQRapid RH® ManualsDownload LiteratureSubmit a Support Ticket CloseMoisture MetersOrion MetersShop NowWhy Buy a Wagner Meter?Learn MoreCompare MetersMoisture Meter ReviewsSupportAccessoriesApps for Mobile DevicesSmart Logger™Learn MoreWood ArticlesTraining/CoursesSpecies Settings & ManualsDownload LiteratureFree Guide to Avoiding Flooring FailuresMoisture Matters NewsletterEasy On-Site Calibration ProcessBecome a Wagner Meters Authorized DistributorChoose Your IndustryWood Flooring Contractors and InstallersFlooring, Millwork, Furniture and Cabinet ManufacturersSmall Sawmill OperationsWoodworking ProfessionalsMusical Instrument Manufacturer and LuthiersBuilding Restoration and Inspection Professionals CloseForest ProductsProducts/SystemsIn-Line Moisture MeasurementIn-Kiln Moisture MeasurementHandheld Moisture MetersAll ProductsResourcesForest Products ArticlesForest Products NewsletterKiln Drying ForumSupport & TrainingDownload LiteratureDownload Catalog CloseShopRapid RH® and Concrete ProductsWood Moisture MetersBuilding Inspection ToolsForest Products Shop CloseAbout UsAssociationsTestimonialsWagner Meters NewsroomBecome a Wagner Meters Authorized Distributor CloseSupport
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy. The personal information we are requesting is for use in our in-house marketing efforts. We never reveal, share, or sell customer information.
We’re strongly committed to safeguarding our customers’ privacy. We operate under the following set of strict privacy principles:
That information is never revealed, resold, or made public for any reason.
Personally identifiable information provided by our customers (name, e-mail or home address, etc.) is never disclosed to anyone.
We use personally identifiable information to process orders.
If you have explicitly subscribed to our newsletters, we will use your personal information only to send you said newsletters.
Cookies and Other Technologies
To enhance your online experience, we use “cookies” or similar technologies. Cookies are text files placed in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information; however, once you choose to furnish a site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site and Internet usage and to improve or customize the content, offerings or advertisements on our sites. We also may use cookies to help us offer you products, programs, or services that may be of interest to you and to deliver relevant advertising.
We, our third party service providers, advertisers or our partners also may use cookies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by Wagner Meters. This also helps us, our service providers and partners provide more relevant advertising.
This website uses Google AdWords.
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Wagner Meters website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page.
As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.
We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Wagner Meters may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.
In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Wagner Meters website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.
Email Information
This website uses Hubspot for marketing purposes. We collect name and email address when you sign up for any of our newsletters.
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone. This also applies when you register for our website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address or make a purchase on this site. For further information see the email policies below.
How Do We Use the Information You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our operations, fulfilling orders, providing customer service and making available other items and services to our audience.
We will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so—in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Email Policies
We are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential. We do not sell, rent, or lease our subscription lists to third parties, and we will not provide your personal information to any third party individual, government agency, or company at any time unless strictly compelled to do so by law.
We will use your e-mail address solely to provide newsletter information to which you have subscribed or for legitimate interest communication.
We will maintain the information you send via e-mail in accordance with applicable federal law.
CAN-SPAM Compliance
In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mail sent from our organization will clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also contain concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further e-mail communication from us.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us by reading the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of any e-mail they receive from us at any time.
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail.
Right to Your Personal Information
If at any time, you would like to view or update your saved personal information, contact us at info@wagnermeters.com and we will supply you with a list of the information we have and what it is being used for. At that time, you may also send us any updates to your information.
Right to Be Forgotten
If you would like us to delete all your personal information, send us an email at info@wagnermeters.com. Once your personal data has been deleted, we will not be able to recover it at a later date.
If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to contact us.
Subscribe
Wagner Meters Newsletter
Connect with Us Follow Us on Social Media
Get in Touch Wagner Meters
326 Pine Grove Road
Rogue River, Oregon 97537 USA
Phone 800-634-9961
info@wagnermeters.com
About
Copyright © 2020 Wagner Meters|Warranty|Return Policy|Terms & Conditions|Privacy Policy
Orders received after 12pm PST on December 10th through December 11th will be shipped on December 14th.
+
We use cookies to personalize your shopping data and ads. We may share your information with our social media, advertising, and analytics partners. If you continue using our site you consent to our cookies. Read More
